https://www.mortgageledger.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy Policy Privacy Policyswitzman2018-08-29T20:30:30-04:00OVERVIEWMortgage Ledger, an EMR Publishing, LLC. subsidiary has created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for this website.COLLECTION AND RETENTION OF INFORMATION BY MORTGAGE LEDGERMortgage Ledger may require that you provide certain identifying information (“personally identifiable information”) such as name, address, telephone number and email address to gain access to one of our products or services or to enhance your experience on our site.Subscribers receiving email delivery of Mortgage Ledger’ newsletters and those using the online archives: Mortgage Ledger may use tracking software in order to ensure accurate use and copyright compliance. This software accesses usage information from the computers of the original and any subsequent users of our electronic material and makes the information available to Mortgage Ledger.USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTEDIn accordance with the terms stated in this privacy policy, Mortgage Ledger may from time to time use information collected from its customers and/or website users for the following:Informational, marketing and promotional purposes on behalf of Mortgage Ledger’s products and services, Mortgage Ledger’s partners and third parties, including such benefits as any future free services, informing you of service enhancements or promotional items;To disclose that information to third parties when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Mortgage Ledger’s rights or property, other members or users of MortgageLedger.com or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities; andTo disclose that information to third parties when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law or a court of competent jurisdiction.ANONYMOUS INFORMATIONMortgage Ledger may gather anonymous information that may be used by the company or shared with third parties. This information does not personally identify you but may be helpful for improving the services we offer. Generally, this information is collected through traffic data.We collect only the IP address, which sometimes can be converted to a domain name, but not the email address of visitors to our web page, aggregate information on what consumers access or visit; and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.SALE OF ASSETSAs Mortgage Ledger continues to develop its business, we may sell or buy other businesses or assets. A buyer or successor will have access to information collected on our website, as this is considered a transferable business asset.OPTING OUTFrom time to time, Mortgage Ledger will send you email newsletters, product announcements, surveys or other information via email. If you prefer not to receive any or all of these communications, you may opt out by following the directions provided within the email newsletters.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.PRODUCTS AND SERVICESThroughout the site, we mention organizations, products, and services that might interest users. This does not signify our endorsement of them. The fact that a certain organization, product, or service is not listed on our site may mean that we are not aware of its existence.CHILDRENMortgageLedger.com is not directed to individuals younger than 18 years of age, and Mortgage Ledger does not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from such individuals.SECURITYWe have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number. We use industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls and secure socket layers where appropriate. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the internet.Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal, regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. Third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can disclose (and you authorize us to do so) any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials, as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICYMortgage Ledger reserves the right to change or update this privacy policy at any time with reasonable notice to the users of the site. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the site. A “user” is a person who visits any portion of the website, and a “person” (you) means an individual, a partnership, a joint venture, a corporation, a trust, an estate, an unincorporated organization or any other entity, or a government or any department or agency thereof.WHOM TO CONTACTIf you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please submit them to webmaster@mortgageledger.com and include “Privacy Policy” as the subject heading.© Copyright 2018 Mortgage Ledger, an EMR Publishing, LLC. subsidiary
Go to Top
